# Corinne Bradford

linkedin.com/in/cori-bradford github.com/coribradford

## Software Engineering Intern

Upcoming graduate offering a strong foundation in software engineering and programming fundamentals across multiple platforms. Experienced in object-oriented programming, developing, testing, and debugging code. Utilizes interpersonal skills to consult with internal and external clients to ensure end-user satisfaction. Quick learner with an aptitude for mastering new technologies and a demonstrated ability to work both independently and in a team.

#### Education

**B.S. Computer Science Software Engineering -** Oregon State University - Cascades

Academic Honors: 3.8 GPA, Dean's List (3 Terms), Tau Beta Pi Honor Society

Bend, Oregon

Relevant Coursework:

- Software Engineering
- Software Development
- Business of Software
- Data Structures

- Analysis of Algorithms
- Network Security
- Machine Learning & Data Mining
- Cloud Application Development (AWS)

## **Relevant Work Experience**

Student Project Consultant (Intern), OSU-Cascades Innovation Co-Lab - Bend, Oregon

Dec 2021–Present

- Coordinate with software development team to assess and meet client needs
- Assist clients in developing a Scope of Work Functional Specification document to aid and direct software design

#### Student Teaching Assistant, OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Jan 2021-Dec 2021

- Courses taught: Introduction to Computer Science 1, Introduction to Computer Science 2, Data Structures
- Debugged, tested, and assessed Python and Java programming assignments for classes of 30+ students
- Conducted weekly study groups, explained concepts and assisted in labs, projects, and other related materials to enhance student engagement and understanding of material

## **Projects**

#### Ecotone (Capstone Project), OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Sept 2021–Present

- Ongoing full stack development of a web application to record and display plants on university campus; application utilized by Biology and Natural Resources Departments for lab purposes
- Applying interpersonal skills to coordinate with a team of four in the process of updating libraries and functionality in a legacy rails application
- Assisting team in assessment, implementation, and testing of new features
- Utilizing Basecamp project management software and Agile software development process

#### Smart Dog Collar (Research Assistant), OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Jan 2021-Oct 2021

- Research project to construct a smart dog collar using arduino microcontroller and sensors
- Utilized data collected from prototypes and Machine Learning algorithms to detect and correctly identify seizures in canines
- Assessed data recorded with an alpha prototype using Tensorflow libraries

Anticipated Dec 2022

- Designed and developed a web application to display information and photos from Wikipedia
- Utilized HTML/CSS, Python, and Flask frameworks, and integrated external APIs to interface with Wikipedia and embed YouTube videos
- Developed using Jira project management software and the Agile software development process

### **Volunteer and Activities**

#### Hacker Refactor Club (ACM-W) - Officer, OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Sept 2020–Present

- Provide opportunities for students to explore the field of computer science and develop professional skills through community outreach, teaching at local K-12 schools
- Host study sessions for STEM students
- Organize professional development workshops

## **Technical Skills**

Python	Ruby	Rails
HTML/CSS	MySQL	PostgreSQL
Tensorflow	Git/GitHub	CI/CD

## **Other Work Experience**

Sales Associate/Bartender, Modern Games - Bend, Oregon	April 2019–March 2020
Assistant Assistant Manager, McMenamins Old Saint Francis Pub - Bend, Oregon	April 2017–August 2018
Front of House Manager, Mio Sushi - Bend, Oregon	November 2016–April 2017
Bartender, Paradise Creek - Pullman, Washington	October 2014–May 2016
Host, The Hamilton - Washington, D.C.	August 2013–December 2013